Guide to the H.E Butti Bin Bishr Collection AD.MC.093
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Festivals and Delegations
  - Top, from the left: H.H. Sheikh Mubarak Al Nahyan, Ahmad Bin Mohammed Al Masaood, and H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki at an Al Ayala dance. Bottom right: a studio portrait of an unidentified man and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right)., Circa 1963-1964; AD_MC_093_ref13_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 2
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Ad-Dammān, Saudi Arabia; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Dancing; Painted Backdrops; Facial Hair; Crowds; Gatherings; Carpets/Rugs; Royalty
  - From the top down: a group of men at an Al Ayala dance; a group portrait, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (first row, second from the right) on his first day working for Sheikh Zayed; from the left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, two unidentified men, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem, and an unidentified man receiving a delegation from a foreign country., Circa 1963-1964, Circa 1965-1966, Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref13_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Dancing; Gatherings; Boys; Children; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - From the top down: two views of H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki dancing Al Ayala with a boy, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr carrying a sword next to an unidentified man at an Al Ayala dance., Circa 1963-1964; AD_MC_093_ref13_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Boys; Children; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Gatherings; Crowds; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Dancing; Swords/Knives; Weapons; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Girls; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates
  - Top: a gathering for the reception of Hussein, King of Jordan, (H.E. Butti Bin Bishr and H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki stand behind him). Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting Hussein, King of Jordan and the Jordanian delegation, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr and H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki in the background., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref13_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Microphones; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Airports; Ceremonies; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Political Leadership; Hussein, King of Jordan, 1935-1999; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - Left image, from the left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.H. Sheikh Rashid Bin Saeed, Sheikh Khalifa Bin Hamad Al Thani of Qatar, an unidentified man, and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan. Right image: a studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1969-1971; AD_MC_093_ref13_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Studio Photography; Group Portraits; Men; Individual Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Boys; Children; Facial Hair; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr sitting at his desk with Ali Al Sayar and two other men at his office in Al Ain., 1967-1968; AD_MC_093_ref13_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Offices; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Furnishings; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Telephones; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates
  - Top left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at an Al Ayala dance. Top right: H.H. Sheikh Mubarak Al Nahyan and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at an Al Ayala dance., Circa 1966-1967; AD_MC_093_ref13_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dancing; Gatherings; Group Portraits; Men; Guns; Weapons; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Royalty
  - Top: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at an Al Ayala dance. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Khalid Bin Mohammed Al Qasimi with a group of men behind him, including Sheikh Ahmad Bin Ali Al Thani (right) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left)., Circa 1966; AD_MC_093_ref13_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Gatherings; Dancing; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Buildings; Architecture; Crowds; Boys; Children; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Royalty; Political Leadership; Sheikh, Ahmad bin Ali bin Abdullah bin Jassim bin Mohammed Al Thani, 1922-1977; Khalid bin Mohammed Al Qasimi, Sheikh, 1931-1972
  - From the top left clockwise: from the left: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan meeting Sheikh Khalifa Bin Hamad Al Thani and Sheikh Ahmad Bin Ali Al Thani of Qatar by an airplane; men performing an Al Ayala dance; and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr and Sheikh Hasher Bin Maktoum Al Maktoum., Circa 1969-1970, Circa 1966, Circa 1965-1966; AD_MC_093_ref13_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Facial Hair; Airplanes; Transportation; Arabic Writing; Military/Soldiers; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Crowds; Architecture; Buildings; Furnishings; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Dancing; Political Leadership; Sheikh, Ahmad bin Ali bin Abdullah bin Jassim bin Mohammed Al Thani, 1922-1977; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the top clockwise: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Khalifa Bin Hamad Al Thani of Qatar outside the Abu Dhabi Airport, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) and a group of men at pre-unification talks, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in a garden; and H.E. Lieutenant General Khalfan Al Romaithi and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) with two other men., Circa 1967-1966, Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref13_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Airports; Facial Hair; Flags; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; United Arab Emirates; Presidents; Officials; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Microphones; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Gatherings; Individual Portraits; Electricity; Gardens; Cigarettes; Smoking; Furnishings; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the top clockwise: a studio portrait of Sheikh Hasher Bin Maktoum Al Maktoum; H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a staircase with H.H. Sheikh Khalid Bin Mohammed Al Qasimi, the ruler of Fujairah; and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at an Al Ayala dance., Circa 1963-1964; AD_MC_093_ref13_000018_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Group Portraits; Men; Studio Photography; Dancing; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Facial Hair; Presidents; Royalty; Cameras; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; United Arab Emirates; Political Leadership; Khalid bin Mohammed Al Qasimi, Sheikh, 1931-1972; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the top down: From the left: H.H. Sheikh Rashid Bin Humaid Al Nuaimi, H.H. Sheikh Khalid Bin Mohammed Al Qasimi, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.H. Sheikh Saif Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr; H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi talking with two officials; from the left: H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, H.H. Sheikh Suroor Bin Mohammed Bin Khalifa Al Nahyan, H.H. Sheikh Khalifa Bin Zayed Al Nahyan, and H.E. Khalifa Bin Yousef at a pre-unification talk., Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref13_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Flags; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Airports; Furnishings; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; United Arab Emirates; Political Leadership; Khalid bin Mohammed Al Qasimi, Sheikh, 1931-1972; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi (middle), H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right), and Mohammed Badr (second from the left) talking with two unidentified men at a pre-unification meeting., Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref13_000020_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Cameras; Tea/Coffee; Drinks/Beverages; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Smoking; Cigarettes
  - Top: from the left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and Emir Isa Bin Salman Al Khalifa of Bahrain. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan in a car, with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr speaking to him through the window., Circa 1970s; AD_MC_093_ref13_000021_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Streets/Roads; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Facial Hair; Boys; Children; Clocks/Watches; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Political Leadership; Isa bin Salman Al Khalifa, Emir, 1931-1999; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - Top: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) in the United Kingdom on the visit to the British Aircraft Corporation. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Ahmed Bin Ali Al Thani of Qatar with the Emirati military., Circa 1969-1971; AD_MC_093_ref13_000022_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; London, England, UK; Qatar; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Weapons; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Factories; Flags; Ceremonies; Presidents; Royalty; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - Top: A group of tribesmen and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at Sheikh Zayed's majilis. Bottom: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr with a group of military personnel from the court of Sheikh Zayed at his majilis., Circa 1970s; AD_MC_093_ref13_000023_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Children; Boys; Majilis; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Electricity; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Smoking; Cigarettes; Carpets/Rugs; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - Top: H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki (second from the left) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (third from right) in a group of men gathered for a pre-unification conference. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) at a gathering., Circa 1968-1969, 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref13_000024_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Unknown Locations; Flags; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Drinks/Beverages; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - The inside back cover of "Festivals and Delegations from the 1960s and early 1970s.", Circa 1960-1971; AD_MC_093_ref13_000025_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    United Arab Emirates; Qatar; Saudi Arabia; Unknown Locations; London, England, UK
  - The back cover of "Festivals and Delegations from the 1960s and early 1970s.", Circa 1960-1971; AD_MC_093_ref13_000026_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.5 x 29.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Docks/Piers/Jetties; United Arab Emirates; Saudi Arabia; London, England, UK; Qatar; Unknown Locations
- H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Sheikh Al Sabah (Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah) of Kuwait in 1969
  - The front cover of the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Sheikh Al Sabah (Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah) of Kuwait in 1969.", AD_MC_093_ref14_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.3 x 38.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Arabic Calligraphy; Kuwait; Medals/Insignia
  - The inside front cover of the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Sheikh Al Sabah (Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah) of Kuwait in 1969.", AD_MC_093_ref14_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Kuwait
  - A blank page in the album "H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to Sheikh Al Sabah (Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah) of Kuwait in 1969.", AD_MC_093_ref14_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Kuwait; Facial Hair; Presidents; Royalty; Cameras; Gatherings; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting an unidentified man., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Presidents; Royalty; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Kuwait; Gatherings; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah receiving gifts from two Kuwaiti school girls., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Girls; Children; Airports; Airplanes; Transportation; Ceremonies; Kuwait; Gatherings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Arabic Writing; Cameras; Royalty; Presidents; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Hats; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Political Leadership; Sabah Al-Salim Al-Sabah, Sheikh, 1913-1977; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah at the reception of the UAE delegation, with H.E. Lieutenant General Khalfan Al Romaithi and the Abu Dhabi delegation in the background., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Presidents; Royalty; Ceremonies; Kuwait; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Hats; Officials; Political Leadership; Sabah Al-Salim Al-Sabah, Sheikh, 1913-1977; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah walking by the Kuwaiti military at the Kuwait International Airport, including H.E. Khulfan Romaithi behind Sheikh Zayed., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Kuwait; Airports; Ceremonies; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Flags; Presidents; Royalty; Political Leadership; Sabah Al-Salim Al-Sabah, Sheikh, 1913-1977; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting the Kuwaiti delegation, with Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah on the right., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Presidents; Royalty; Ceremonies; Cameras; Kuwait; Political Leadership; Sabah Al-Salim Al-Sabah, Sheikh, 1913-1977; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting the Kuwaiti delegation, with Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah on the right., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Kuwait; Ceremonies; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Political Leadership; Sabah Al-Salim Al-Sabah, Sheikh, 1913-1977; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - A group portrait of members of the UAE delegation including H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi (middle), H.E. Butti Bin Bishr speaking to three men, and H.H. Sheikh Saif Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan (right)., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Ceremonies; Kuwait; Royalty
  - H.E. Khalifa Bin Yousef Al Suwaidi (far left) and a group of men from the Kuwaiti delegation., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Gatherings; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Kuwait
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan talking with members of the Kuwaiti delegation in a tent, with H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi and H.H. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Khalid Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on the left., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tents; Carpets/Rugs; Group Portraits; Men; Presidents; Royalty; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Kuwait; Officials; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a tour, with H.H. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Khalid Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, and H.E. Lieutenant General Khalfan Al Romaithi behind him., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Kuwait; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan sitting on a couch with Jaber Al Ahmad Al Sabah., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Presidents; Royalty; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Kuwait; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting members of the Kuwaiti delegation with Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Kuwait; Gatherings; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah walking with members of the Kuwaiti delegation, including H.E. Lieutenant General Khalfan Al Romaithi (left of Sheikh Zayed) and Nawaf Al Ahmad Al Jaber Al Sabah (middle, second row) in the background., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Kuwait; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Political Leadership; Sabah Al-Salim Al-Sabah, Sheikh, 1913-1977; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Nawaf Al-Ahmad Al-Jaber Al-Sabah, Emir of Kuwait, 1937-
  - A Kuwaiti man giving H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan a tour of a factory., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000018_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Presidents; Royalty; Kuwait; Clocks/Watches; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Factories; Medals/Insignia; Officials; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah on a factory tour with members of the UAE delegation, with Nawaf Al Ahmad Al Jaber Al Sabah in the background., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Factories; Kuwait; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Crowds; Political Leadership; Sabah Al-Salim Al-Sabah, Sheikh, 1913-1977; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Nawaf Al-Ahmad Al-Jaber Al-Sabah, Emir of Kuwait, 1937-
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan with members of the Kuwaiti delegation at the Kuwaiti International Airport., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000020_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Kuwait; Furnishings; Gatherings; Ceremonies; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Airports; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Sheikh Sabah III Al-Salim Al-Sabah in the foreground, with Jaber Al Ahmed Al Sabah and Nawaf Al Ahmad Al Jaber Al Sabah behind them., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref14_000021_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 28.2 x 33.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)